A Guide to the Island Resources Foundation records FA1200
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Projects and Occasional Papers, 1894-1895, 1946, 1956, 1961-1964, 1968-2016; 3; 33.3 Cubic Feet 85 letter document boxes, 1 half-letter document box, and 1 flat file folder
  - #76, United Nations Development Programme (UNDP), Fiji Environmental Consulting, Final Report, 1981 (Box 82, Folder 812)
  - #76, United Nations Development Programme (UNDP), Fiji Environmental Consulting, Correspondence with United Nations Development Programme, 1980-1981 (Box 82, Folder 813)
  - #77, Bonnet & Center for Energy and Environment Research, Final Report, 1981 (Box 82, Folder 814)
  - #77, Bonnet & Center for Energy and Environment Research, Proposal and Purchase Order, 1977, 1980 (Box 82, Folder 815)
  - #78, West Indian Wooden Cottage, Vernacular Architecture, 1992 (Box 82, Folder 816)
  - #78, West Indian Wooden Cottage, Vernacular Architecture-West Indian Wooden Cottage Vernacular Architecture in the Virgin Islands, 1992 (Box 82, Folder 816)
  - #78, West Indian Wooden Cottage, Vernacular Architecture-The West Indian Wooden Cottage (Box 82, Folder 816)
  - #78, West Indian Wooden Cottage, Vernacular Architecture-West Indian Wooden Cottage Vernacular Architecture of the VI, 1992 July (Box 82, Folder 816)
  - #78, West Indian Wooden Cottage, Vernacular Architecture-West Indian Wooden Cottage Vernacular Architecture in the Virgin Islands, 1992 July (Box 82, Folder 816)
  - #78, West Indian Wooden Cottage, Vernacular Architecture-The West Indian Wooden Cottage, Vernacular Architecture in the U. S. Virgin Islands, 28 minutes; U-matic (Box 1, Tape AV 11888)
  - #78, West Indian Wooden Cottage, Vernacular Architecture-The West Indian Wooden Cottage, Vernacular Architecture in the Virgin Islands, 1992 July 8; VHS; 28 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 11889)
  - #78, West Indian Wooden Cottage, Vernacular Architecture-The West Indian Wooden Cottage, Vernacular Architecture in the Virgin Islands, 1992 July 8; VHS; 28 minutes (Box 2, Tape AV 11890)
  - #80, Cultural Resource Development Planning, Proposal, 1979-1981 (Box 82, Folder 817)
  - #80, Cultural Resource Development Planning, Correspondence with Rockefeller Brothers Fund (RBF), 1981-1985 (Box 82, Folder 818)
  - #80, Cultural Resource Development Planning, Resource Participant Correspondence, 1983 (Box 82, Folder 819)
  - #80, Cultural Resource Development Planning, Correspondence with St. Kitts, 1983-1984 (Box 82, Folder 820)
  - #80, Cultural Resource Development Planning, Correspondence with Caribbean Conservation Association and Eastern Caribbean Natural Area Management Program, 1982-1984 (Box 83, Folder 821)
  - #80, Cultural Resource Development Planning, General Correspondence, 1981-1984 (Box 83, Folder 822)
  - #80, Historical Resource Development Planning, Workshop Agenda, Program, 1983 (Box 83, Folder 823)
  - #80, Historical Resource Development Planning, Workshop Mailing List, 1983, 1985 (Box 83, Folder 824)
  - #80, Historical Resource Development Planning, Press Releases and Publicity, 1983 (Box 83, Folder 825)
  - #80, Historical Resource Development Planning, Brimstone Hill Workshop, 1982-1983 (Box 83, Folder 826)
  - #80A, Cabrits, Dominica, Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 83, Folder 827)
  - #80A, Cabrits, Dominica, Final Report, 1982-1983 (Box 83, Folder 828-829)
  - #80A, Cabrits, Dominica, Final Report, Report Contact Sheets, 1982 (Box 191, Folder 2201)
  - #80A, Cabrits, Dominica, Final Report, Negatives, 1982 (Box 191, Folder 2202)
  - #82, Virgin Islands Vessel Waste Plan, 1983 (Box 83, Folder 830)
  - #82, Virgin Islands Vessel Waste Plan, 1983 (Box 84, Folder 831)
  - #83, Coastal Dunes for Protection and Sand Resources, 1983 (Box 84, Folder 832)
  - #86, National Park Service (NPS) Case Studies, Coastal Resources, Background Information, 1982-1983 (Box 84, Folder 833)
  - #86, National Park Service (NPS) Case Studies, Coastal Resources, Proposal #7, Fisheries, 1982 (Box 84, Folder 835)
  - #86, National Park Service (NPS) Case Studies, Coastal Resources, Fisheries, Questionnaire, 1983-1984 (Box 84, Folder 835)
  - #86, National Park Service (NPS) Case Studies, Coastal Resources, Proposal No. 3, Sand Mining, 1982 (Box 84, Folder 836)
  - #86, National Park Service (NPS) Case Studies, Coastal Resources, Proposal No. 10, Island Microcosm, 1982 (Box 84, Folder 837)
  - #86, National Park Service (NPS) Case Studies, Coastal Resources, Internal Memorandum, Documents, etc., 1982-1983 (Box 84, Folder 838)
  - #86, National Park Service (NPS) Case Studies, Coastal Resources, Monthly Progress Reports, 1983-1984 (Box 84, Folder 839)
  - #86, National Park Service (NPS) Case Studies, Coastal Resources, Correspondence with the National Park Service, 1982-1984 (Box 84, Folder 841)
  - #86, National Park Service (NPS) Case Studies, Coastal Resources, Best and Final Offer, 1982 (Box 84, Folder 842)
  - #86, National Park Service (NPS) Case Studies, Coastal Resources, Contract Documents, 1983-1984 (Box 84, Folder 843)
  - #86, National Park Service (NPS) Case Studies, Coastal Resources, Island Microcosm, 1984 (Box 84, Frame 844)
  - #86, National Park Service (NPS) Case Studies, Coastal Resources, Coral Harvesting and Sand Mining Management Practices, 1984 (Box 84, Folder 845)
  - #86, National Park Service (NPS) Case Studies, Coastal Resources, Coastal Management, Lessons Learned from the Caribbean, 1984 (Box 84, Folder 846)
  - #88, Virgin Islands Biosphere Reserve Workshop Video, National Park Service Correspondence, 1983-1984, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 847)
  - #88, Virgin Islands Biosphere Reserve Workshop Video, National Park Service Correspondence-Man & Biosphere Reserve, VI National Park, 1983 (Box 85, Folder 847)
  - #88, Virgin Islands Biosphere Reserve Workshop Video, National Park Service Correspondence-The West Indian Wooden Cottage, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 847)
  - #88, Virgin Islands Biosphere Reserve Workshop Video, National Park Service Correspondence-VINP-Biosphere Reserve Dedication, 1983 (Box 85, Folder 847)
  - #88, Virgin Islands Biosphere Reserve Workshop Video, National Park Service Correspondence-Bio Reserve, U-matic (Box 2, Tape AV 11891)
  - #88, Virgin Islands Biosphere Reserve Workshop Video, General Correspondence, 1983 (Box 85, Folder 848)
  - #88, Virgin Islands Biosphere Reserve Workshop Video, Income, 1983-1984 (Box 85, Folder 849)
  - #88, Virgin Islands Biosphere Reserve Workshop Video, Sub-Contract with Studio Five, 1983 (Box 85, Folder 851)
  - #88, Virgin Islands Biosphere Reserve Workshop Video (Box 85, Folder 851)
  - #89, MAB, The United States National Committee for Man and the Biosphere, 1977-1979 (Box 85, Folder 852)
  - #89, MAB, The United States National Committee for Man and the Biosphere, Island Conference Correspondence, 1982-1986 (Box 85, Folder 853)
  - #89, MAB, The United States National Committee for Man and the Biosphere, Solid Waste Project Correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 85, Folder 857)
  - #89, MAB, The United States National Committee for Man and the Biosphere, Invoices, 1983-1989 (Box 85, Folder 858)
  - #90, Artemia, General Correspondence, 1982-1985 (Box 85, Folder 859)
  - #90, Artemia, Correspondence with the University of West Indies, Euna Moore, 1982-1985 (Box 85, Folder 860)
  - #90, Artemia, Reports to US Agency for International Development, 1984 (Box 85, Folder 861)
  - #90, Artemia, Internal Correspondence and Reports, 1983-1984 (Box 85, Folder 862)
  - #90, Artemia, Reports, 1983-1984, 1987 (Box 85, Folder 863)
  - #90, Artemia, Correspondence with Patrick Sorgeloos, 1982-1985 (Box 85, Folder 864)
  - #90, Artemia, Grant Award Documents, 1983-1984 (Box 85, Folder 865)
  - #90, Artemia, Proposal and Related Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 85, Folder 866)
  - #90, Artemia, Background Information, 1984 (Box 85, Folder 867)
  - #90, Artemia, Assessment of the Mariculture Potential of Indigenous Eastern Caribbean Brine Shrimp, 1984 (Box 85, Folder 868)
  - #91, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) I, Personnel, 1985 (Box 85, Folder 869)
  - #91, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) I, Yale University Project, Correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 85, Folder 870)
  - #91, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) I, Synthesis Report, 1985 (Box 85, Folder 871)
  - #91, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) I, Marine Resources Studies, Sub_Tasks, Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 86, Folder 872)
  - #91, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) I, Marine Resources Studies, Virgin Islands Biosphere Reserve (VIBR), Sub-Contractors, West Indies Laboratory, 1984-1985 (Box 86, Folder 873)
  - #91, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) I, Marine Resource Studies, Virgin Islands Biosphere Reserve (VIBR), Sub-Contractors, Division of Fish and Wildlife, 1983-1985 (Box 86, Folder 874)
  - #91, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) I, Marine Resource Studies, Virgin Islands Biosphere Reserve (VIBR), Sub-Contractors, Caribbean Research Institute, 1983-1985 (Box 86, Folder 875)
  - #91, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) I, Marine Resource Studies, Virgin Islands Biosphere Reserve (VIBR), Sub-Contractor Negotiations, 1983-1984 (Box 86, Folder 877)
  - #91, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) I, Marine Resource Studies, Virgin Islands Biosphere Reserve (VIBR), Correspondence with Virgin Islands National Park (VINP), 1983-1984, 1986 (Box 86, Folder 876)
  - #91, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) I, Marine Resource Studies, Virgin Islands Biosphere Reserve (VIBR), Sub-Contract, 1983-1984 (Box 86, Folder 878)
  - #91, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) I, Marine Resource Studies, Virgin Islands Biosphere Reserve (VIBR), Project Pert Charts, Time Lines, 1984 (Box 86, Folder 879)
  - #91, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) I, Marine Resource Studies, Virgin Islands Biosphere Reserve (VIBR), Progress and Fiscal Reports to the National Park Service, 1984-1986 (Box 86, Folder 880)
  - #91, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) I, Marine Resource Studies, Virgin Islands Biosphere Reserve (VIBR), Correspondence with National Park Service (NPS), 1983-1986 (Box 86, Folder 881)
  - #91, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) I, Marine Resource Studies, Virgin Islands Biosphere Reserve (VIBR), Contract Award Documents, 1983 (Box 86, Folder 882)
  - #91, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) I, Marine Resource Studies, Virgin Islands Biosphere Reserve (VIBR), Proposal, 1983 (Box 86, Folder 883)
  - #91, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) I, Marine Resource Studies, Virgin Islands Biosphere Reserve (VIBR), Request for Workplan, 1983 (Box 86, Folder 884)
  - #91, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) I, Research Report 1 and Abstracts, 1986, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 885)
  - #91, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) I, Research Report 2 and 3, 1986 (Box 86, Folder 886)
  - #91, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) I, Research Report 4, 1986 (Box 87, Folder 887)
  - #91, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) I, Research Report 5-7, 1986 (Box 87, Folder 888)
  - #91, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) I, Research Report 8-10, 1986 (Box 87, Folder 889)
  - #91, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) I, Research Report 11 and 12, 1986 (Box 87, Folder 890)
  - #91, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) I, Research Report 13 and 14, 1986 (Box 87, Folder 891)
  - #91, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) I, Research Report 15-18B, 1987 (Box 87, Folder 892)
  - #91, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) I, Research Report 15-18B, 1987 (Box 88, Folder 893)
  - #91, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) I, Research Report 19-22, 1987 (Box 88, Folder 894-895)
  - #91, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) I, Research Report 23-28, 1988 (Box 88, Folder 896-897)
  - #91, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) I, Research Report 23-26 (Originals), 1988 (Box 88, Folder 898)
  - #91, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) I, Research Report 27-28 (Originals), 1988 (Box 89, Folder 899)
  - #91, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) I, Research Report 29, 1988 (Box 89, Folder 900-901)
  - #91, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) I, Report Covers, 1986, 1988 (Box 89, Folder 902)
  - #93, Fountain Valley Model Environmental Impact Assessment, Proposal and Contract, 1984 (Box 89, Folder 903)
  - #93, Fountain Valley Model Environmental Impact Assessment, Reports, 1984 (Box 89, Folder 904)
  - #93, Fountain Valley Model Environmental Impact Assessment, Correspondence with Contractor, 1984-1985 (Box 89, Folder 905)
  - #94, Crown Bay Marine Archaeological Survey, Proposal(s) and Contract, 1983-1984 (Box 89, Folder 906)
  - #94, Crown Bay Marine Archaeological Survey, Correspondence with Port Authority, 1983-1984 (Box 89, Folder 907)
  - #94, Crown Bay Marine Archaeological Survey, General Correspondence, 1984 (Box 89, Folder 908)
  - #94, Crown Bay Marine Archaeological Survey, Personnel, 1984 (Box 89, Folder 909)
  - #94, Crown Bay Marine Archaeological Survey, Internal, 1984 (Box 89, Folder 910)
  - #94, Crown Bay Marine Archaeological Survey, Internal, Photographs, 1984 (Box 191, Folder 2203)
  - #94, Crown Bay Marine Archaeological Survey, Final Report, 1984 (Box 89, Folder 911)
  - #95, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) II, Concept Papers and Proposal Contract Award, 1984-1985 (Box 89, Folder 912)
  - #95, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) II, Request for Work Plan and Cost Statement, 1984 (Box 89, Folder 913)
  - #95, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) II, General Correspondence, 1985-1987 (Box 89, Folder 914)
  - #95, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) II, Correspondence with National Park Service, 1983-1987 (Box 89, Folder 915)
  - #95, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) II, Virgin Islands Nation Park (VINP) Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 89, Folder 916)
  - #95, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) II, Correspondence, Video Tape Production, 1983-1985, 1987 (Box 89, Folder 917)
  - #95, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) II, Sub-Contractor General Correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 90, Folder 918)
  - #95, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) II, Sub-Contract with Eastern Caribbean Natural Area Management Program (ECNAMP), 1985-1987 (Box 90, Folder 919)
  - #95, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) II, Project No. 3, Caroline Rogers, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 920)
  - #95, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) II, Sub-Contract with College of the Virgin Islands, 1985-1987 (Box 90, Folder 921)
  - #95, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) II, Sub-Contract with George Tyson, 1985-1986 (Box 90, Folder 922)
  - #95, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) II, Sub-Contract with West Indies Laboratory, 1984-1987 (Box 90, Folder 923)
  - #95, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) II, Sub-Contract with the Division of Fish and Wildlife, 1985-1986 (Box 90, Folder 924)
  - #95, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) II, National Park Service Progress Reports, 1985-1987 (Box 90, Folder 925)
  - #96, East Caribbean Fisheries Assessment, Contract, 1985-1986 (Box 90, Folder 926)
  - #96, East Caribbean Fisheries Assessment, Qualifications Statement, 1984 (Box 90, Folder 927)
  - #96, East Caribbean Fisheries Assessment, Internal Documents, Memoranda, etc., 1985 (Box 90, Folder 929)
  - #96, East Caribbean Fisheries Assessment, Correspondence with Agency for International Development, 1985-1986, 1988 (Box 90, Folder 929)
  - #96, East Caribbean Fisheries Assessment, Proposal and Revisions, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 930)
  - #96, East Caribbean Fisheries Assessment, Fishery Sector Assessment: Antigua/Barbuda, Dominica, Grenada, Monterrat, St. Christopher/Nevis, St. Lucia, St. Vincent & Grenadines, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 931)
  - #96, East Caribbean Fisheries Assessment, Correspondence, 1989 (Box 90, Folder 932)
  - #98, Frigate Bay Case Study, United Nations Development Programme (UNDP), Tourism, Environment, Contract, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 933)
  - #98, Frigate Bay Case Study, United Nations Development Programme (UNDP), Tourism, Environment, Project Personnel, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 934)
  - #98, Frigate Bay Case Study, United Nations Development Programme (UNDP), Tourism, Environment, Correspondence with United Nations Development Programme, 1985-1986 (Box 90, Folder 935)
  - #98, Frigate Bay Case Study, United Nations Development Programme (UNDP), Tourism, Environment, Report, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 936)
  - #99, Eastern Caribbean Natural Area Management Program (ECNAMP) Evaluation, Proposal and Grant Award, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 937)
  - #99, Eastern Caribbean Natural Area Management Program (ECNAMP) Evaluation, Internal, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 938)
  - #99, Eastern Caribbean Natural Area Management Program (ECNAMP) Evaluation, Survey Instruments, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 939)
  - #99, Eastern Caribbean Natural Area Management Program (ECNAMP) Evaluation, Questionnaire Response, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 940)
  - #99, Eastern Caribbean Natural Area Management Program (ECNAMP) Evaluation, General Correspondence, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 941)
  - #99, Eastern Caribbean Natural Area Management Program (ECNAMP) Evaluation, Correspondence with Eastern Caribbean Natural Area Management Program, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 942)
  - #99, Eastern Caribbean Natural Area Management Program (ECNAMP) Evaluation, Correspondence with Funders, 1979-1980, 1984-1985 (Box 91, Folder 943)
  - #99, Eastern Caribbean Natural Area Management Program (ECNAMP) Evaluation, Report, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 944)
  - #100, St. John Plantations, Proposal and Grant Award Document, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 945)
  - #100, St. John Plantations, Correspondence with Funders, 1985-1986 (Box 91, Folder 946)
  - #101, Long Bay Marine Archaeological Survey, Proposal and Related Correspondence, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 947)
  - #101, Long Bay Marine Archaeological Survey, Correspondence, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 948)
  - #101, Long Bay Marine Archaeological Survey, Reports, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 949-950)
  - #102, Coastal Barrier Study, Contract Documents, Correspondence, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 951)
  - #102, Coastal Barrier Study, Contract Documents, Correspondence, Personnel, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 952)
  - #102, Coastal Barrier Study, Contract Documents, Report, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 953)
  - #103, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) III, Contract, 1985-1986 (Box 92, Folder 954)
  - #103, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) III, National Park Service (NPS) Request for Work Plan, Island Resources Foundation Proposal, 1985 (Box 92, Folder 955)
  - #103, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) III, Sub-Contractor Requestion for Work Plan, 1985, 1987 (Box 92, Folder 956)
  - #103, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) III, National Park Service (NPS) Quarterly Progress Reports, 1986-1987 (Box 92, Folder 957)
  - #103, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) III, Correspondence with National Park Service (NPS) and Virgin Islands National Park Service (VINPS), 1986-1989 (Box 92, Folder 958)
  - #103, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) III, Marine Resources Studies, Meetings, 1983-1985, 1987 (Box 92, Folder 959)
  - #103, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) III, General Cooperative Correspondence, 1985-1989 (Box 92, Folder 960)
  - #103, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) III, Personnel, 1987 (Box 92, Folder 961)
  - #103, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) III, Publicity, 1985, 1987, 1989 (Box 92, Folder 962)
  - #103, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) III, Task 1, Database Management, 1985-1988 (Box 92, Folder 963)
  - #103, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) III, Task 2, Resource Management Course, 1985-1988 (Box 92, Folder 964)
  - #103, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) III, Revised Task 3, Salt Pond Sedimentation, 1985-1987 (Box 92, Folder 965)
  - #103, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) III, Task 4, Boating Trends, 1987 (Box 92, Folder 966)
  - #103, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) III, Task 6, Seagrass Beds, 1985-1988 (Box 92, Folder 967)
  - #103, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) III, Task 7, Buck Island, 1985-1988 (Box 92, Folder 968)
  - #103, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) III, Task 10, Vegetation, 1986-1987 (Box 92, Folder 969)
  - #103, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) III, Task 11, Geochemistry, 1985-1987 (Box 92, Folder 970)
  - #103, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) III, Task 11, Synthesis, 1986, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 971)
  - #103, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) III, Task 13, Administration, 1987 (Box 92, Folder 972)
  - #103, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) III, Report Distribution Information, 1987-1989 (Box 92, Folder 973)
  - #103, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) III, Special Report, Management of Natural Resource Information for the Virgin Islands Nation Park (VINP) and Biosphere Reserve, 1988 (Box 93, Folder 974)
  - #105, St. Kitts South East Peninsula and Environmental Assessment, Proposal and Contract Award, 1985 (Box 93, Folder 975)
  - #105, St. Kitts South East Peninsula and Environmental Assessment, Internal Project Documents, 1985 (Box 93, Folder 976)
  - #105, St. Kitts South East Peninsula and Environmental Assessment, Correspondence with St. Kitts Government, 1985-1986 (Box 93, Folder 977)
  - #105, St. Kitts South East Peninsula and Environmental Assessment, Correspondence with US Agency for International Development, 1985-1985 (Box 93, Folder 978)
  - #105, St. Kitts South East Peninsula and Environmental Assessment, Background, 1985 (Box 93, Folder 979)
  - #105, St. Kitts South East Peninsula and Environmental Assessment, Report, 1986 (Box 93, Folder 980-981)
  - #106, Dominica Pesticides Assessment, Proposal and Grant Award Documents, 1985-1986 (Box 93, Folder 982)
  - #106, Dominica Pesticides Assessment, Internal Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 93, Folder 983)
  - #106, Dominica Pesticides Assessment, External Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 93, Folder 984)
  - #106, Dominica Pesticides Assessment, Correspondence with US Agency for International Development, 1986-1987 (Box 93, Folder 985)
  - #106, Dominica Pesticides Assessment, Report, 1987 (Box 93, Folder 986)
  - #107, Crown Bay Bathymetry, Contract and Proposal, 1985-1986 (Box 93, Folder 987)
  - #107, Crown Bay Bathymetry, Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 93, Folder 988)
  - #108, St. Kitts, South East Peninsula, Land Use Management Plan, Statement of Work, Proposal, and Contract, 1986 (Box 93, Folder 989)
  - #108, St. Kitts, South East Peninsula, Land Use Management Plan, Personnel, 1986 (Box 93, Folder 990)
  - #108, St. Kitts, South East Peninsula, Land Use Management Plan, Non-Government/External Correspondence, etc., 1964, 1986 (Box 93, Folder 991)
  - #108, St. Kitts, South East Peninsula, Land Use Management Plan, Internal, 1986 (Box 94, Folder 992)
  - #108, St. Kitts, South East Peninsula, Land Use Management Plan, Landowners' Questionnaire, Correspondence, etc., 1986 (Box 94, Folder 993)